<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<man>
	<entry name="commands">
		<gpath statement="find{it[man.entry.@name]}"/>
	</entry>
	<entry name="look">
		<description>
			A good way to see whats around you.
	
			Looking describes the current room you are in, and helps display the
			important
			exits and anyone that might be in it. It may not show everyone, however!
	
			You can also look at something, or if you fancy having a rummage you
			can look IN something.
	      </description>
		<syntax>
			look | l | look at [something | someone]
			look in [container]
	      </syntax>
		<example>
			look at me
			look in sack
	      </example>
	</entry>
	<entry name="inventory">
		<description>
			Whats in your pockets?
	
			This little command shows you what you are carrying. You can also look
			at yourself,
			but this is generally said to be the briefest way of doing it.
		</description>
		<syntax>inventory inv i</syntax>
		<seealso>look</seealso>
	</entry>
	<entry name="quit">
		<description>
			Feel like logging out? This command is your best buddy.
			How easy could it be?
	
			We obviously don't want you to quit, but its probably best if you want
			to
			continue with any kind of life away from us :)
	</description>
		<syntax>
			quit 
	</syntax>
	</entry>
	<entry name="save">
		<description>
			Feel like saving someone? Try saving yourself!
	
			Saving, er, saves your character for later. 
	</description>
		<syntax>
			save 
	</syntax>
	</entry>
	<entry name="say">
		<description>
			Fancy saying something? Why keep it to yourself?
	
			Saying something is easy with the say command, just say whats on your
			mind! Only people
			in your current room will hear what you have to say. 
	</description>
		<syntax>
			say [sentence]
	</syntax>
		<seealso>
			shout, tell
	</seealso>
	</entry>
	<entry name="who">
		<description>
			Who's online? Whos who in the groovy mud world.
	  	</description>
		<syntax>
			who
	  	</syntax>
	</entry>
	<entry name="drop">
		<description>
			Getting rid of something couldn't be more easy. 
	  	</description>
		<syntax>
			drop [item]
	  	</syntax>
	</entry>
	<entry name="get">
		<description>
			Picking stuff up is great. If its too heavy though, it might slow
			you down!
	</description>
		<syntax>
			get [all | all items | item | items] [from item]		
	</syntax>
		<example>
			get all from sack
			get red banana from sacks
			get all red bananas from blue sack
			get banana
			get blue bananas
	</example>
		<seealso>
			drop, put
	</seealso>
	</entry>
	<entry name="term">
		<description>
			Change your terminal type, it could add colour to your world! Typing
			"term types" will show you the terminal types we support.
	</description>
		<syntax>
			term [terminal name] | types
	</syntax>
		<example>
			term ansi
			term types
	</example>
		<seealso>
		</seealso>
	</entry>
</man>